<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <packageId>Ionfrigate12345.RealisticApparelHeatInsulation</packageId>
    <name>Realistic Apparel Heat Insulation</name>
    <author>Ionfrigate12345</author>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.5</li>
    </supportedVersions>
	<modDependenciesByVersion>
		<v1.5>
			<li>
				<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
				<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
				<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
				<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
			</li>
		</v1.5>
	</modDependenciesByVersion>
    <loadAfter>
        <li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
    </loadAfter>
    <description>WARNING: This is a difficulty mod, unrecommended for new players. It will especially make high temperature biomes MUCH harder. No longer it will be possible to simply wear a bunch of legendary hyperweave or devilstrand apparels with alot of armor values then permanently forget the temperature. 
	But if you love extreme climate challenge, this mod is for you. It will also be more funny to combine it with some others like Yayo's Planet，Climate Cycle++，Adjustable Temperature Events, or simply make heat wave event appear more often in VE Events config.
	
	In Vanilla, the more clothings a pawn wear, the higher their max comfortable temperature becomes. There is no "negative" impact of wearing too much in summer, even a parkas doesn't give you any penalty in a heat wave of 50 celcius. This is unrealistic and immersion breaking. Besides, as we all know, even the same clothing doesn't give you the same heat insulation in different weather, especially humidity. A duster in 40 celcius doesn't result in the same heat insulation in arid desert with clear sky and in rainy jungle. However Vanilla game ignore this factor completely. This mod focus on dealing with this issue by making apparel heat insulation more realistic and challenging. Some previously useless traits like Nudist will also have their place in certain gameplay styles.
	</description>
</ModMetaData>